{
    "subject": "JR_Chandler",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Marissa_Tasker",
    "human_readable": "JR Chandler is married to Marissa Tasker.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9329528212547302,
            "question": "Who is married to Marissa Tasker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9268878102302551,
            "question": "What is the relationship between JR Chandler and Marissa Tasker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9178442358970642,
            "question": "To whom is JR Chandler married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9011903405189514,
            "question": "Who is JR Chandler married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.899095892906189,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between JR Chandler and Marissa Tasker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7364165782928467,
            "question": "What is the name of Marissa Tasker's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6816533803939819,
            "question": "Who is JR Chandler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6448206901550293,
            "question": "Is JR Chandler in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5868635177612305,
            "question": "Name one person connected to Marissa Tasker."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.555870532989502,
            "question": "Is JR Chandler's marital status single?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=JR Chandler is married to Marissa Tasker.",
            "html": "yago_30361_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one person connected to Marissa Tasker.",
            "html": "yago_30361_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is JR Chandler in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30361_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is JR Chandler?",
            "html": "yago_30361_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30361_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information that suggests JR Chandler is married to Marissa Tasker. In the provided context, it mentions that Marissa was previously married to JR Chandler from 2009-2010 but they are divorced. Therefore, the statement \"JR Chandler is married to Marissa Tasker\" is incorrect according to the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}